Huynh Minh Tam

Software Engineer

A passionate software engineer with more than half year of hands-on experience as a FRONT-END developer. My expertise spans Javascript /TypeScript programming languages and extends to another programming languages . Always excited to tackle new challenges in the ever-evolving world of tech.

Work Experience

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam 0823532831 hunhminhtam@gmail.com

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Intern Frontend Developer

FPT software

• At FPT Software, I'm learning to design effective UX/UI, implementing interfaces from Figma, and developing modules like CRUD.

Mar 2024 - Jun 2024 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Frontend Developer

Cydeva technology

 At Cydeva technology. Skilled in developing and maintaining projects. Proficient in both front-end and back-end technologies, with expertise in Typescript/Javascipt programming languages and a bit mobile development.

Education

Dec 2020 - Dec 2024

FPT University
Software Engineering

GPA:8.2/10

Skills

Backend	Frontend	Other
 JavaScipt /TypeScipt 	HTML/CSS	MySQL ,Mongo DB
Java	NextJS / ReactJS	 RabbitMQ
Node js express	 Redux toolkit / Zustand 	Socket IO
	 React Query /SWR 	 Github CI/CD
	 Tailwind CSS / Mui / Ant design 	Cloudinary
		 Github/Gitlab

Projects

Apr 2024 - Present thehostie.com Hostie Fullstack developer	Hostie is my entrepreneurial project aimed at connecting brokers and property owners in the short-term accommodation sector. Utilizing technologies like Golang and Java, Hostie enhances communication and operational efficiency, demonstrating my capability to innovate and integrate advanced solutions in hospitality management	
Jan 2023 – March 2023 Hella Booking Backend Developer	School project .Experienced in Hella backend development, Hella external api development.	
Aug 2024 - Oct 2024 Pc store Fullstack developer	My pet project based on https://tinhocngoisao.com/ . Webapp is a small ecommerce platforms.	

CERTIFICATIONS

Apr 2023	CertNexus Certified Ethical Emerging Technologies
Jan 2023	Software Development Lifecycle
Oct 2022	Web Design for Everybody
Jun 2022	Computer Communications
DEC 2021	Toeic 610

SOCIAL NETWORK

Gitub: https://github.com/TamHM1410

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/toilatam1410/